networkplay.in 2010-11-26

# India’s No.1 Digital Brand Ad-Network

## Privacy Policy

Please read this policy to understand what information Networkplay.in collects, how the information is used, and what choices you have regarding the collection and use of your information when using Networkplay.in.

## Policy Scope

This policy covers information you share, both personally identifiable and non-identifiable information, with Networkplay.in as a visitor to the Networkplay.in web site. 

## Information We Collect

Networkplay.in collects both personally identifiable information as well as non-personally identifiable information.

## Personally Identifiable Information

Personally identifiable information is any information that identifies a specific individual, such as a name, email address, or phone number. 

Networkplay.in collects personally-identifiable information whenever a user submits a comment or a query through the Contact Us page.

Personally identifiable information may be transferred or used by technology service providers that Networkplay.in works with. These providers require access to information in order to provide services to the user. 

## Non-Personally Identifiable Information

The Networkplay.in web site collects non-personally identifiable information on the Networkplay.in web site in the following instances: 

• Log files. The Networkplay.in web site collects information about users and stores it in log files maintained on Networkplay.in and 3rd party equipment. This information includes non-personally identifiable information that your browser automatically sends whenever you visit this site, including information about your web request, your IP address your browser type, browser language, date and time of the request.   
• Cookies. A session cookie is a small text file that the Networkplay.in web site generates and temporarily stores in the memory of the user's computer during the login session. Each time a user logs on to the Networkplay.in web site, the site issues a session cookie. The session cookie is linked to your login and enables Networkplay.in or relevant 3rd parties to monitor the Networkplay.in web site for unauthorized usage. The Networkplay.in web site cookie information is not combined with information from any ad serving cookies.   
• Clear pixels. Clear pixels (also called web beacons and one-by-one pixels) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, that are used to remember the pages or sections of a site that a user visits. The Networkplay.in web site can use clear pixels in order to analyze the performance and usefulness of this site. 

## Information Use

Networkplay.in uses the personally identifiable information you share with us to respond to your query or comment.

Networkplay.in also uses the personally-identifiable information you provide to respond to your inquiries and requests, and to keep accurate records concerning the services you are requesting through the Networkplay.in web site.

All information may be used for additional purposes, such as auditing, research, and development of additional web site capabilities or services. Networkplay.in generally uses non-personally identifiable information in aggregated form to help us measure the web site's performance and effectiveness, and to improve its usefulness. 

## Information Sharing

Networkplay.in does not rent, share, or sell the personally identifiable information you share with us without your prior permission. Personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information may be shared with 3rd party providers, in aggregated or unaggregated fashion. Some or all of the features of Networkplay.in's ad network management services may be provided by 3rd parties. Please note that we may also share information in the event that we are asked to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, or as otherwise permitted by law. If and when we use third parties to assist us in processing your personal information, we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. Networkplay.in may transfer the information it collects to any successor in interest to Networkplay.in (such as a company that acquires Networkplay.in), or internally to one or more affiliates (such as a corporate subsidiary or parent).

## Acceptance of Privacy Policy

When you use the Networkplay.in web site, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and Networkplay.in will have the right to use your information as described in the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy, you must immediately discontinue use of the Networkplay.in web site. Networkplay.in reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of the Networkplay.in web site after a change in the Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of those changes.
